    var frugal = [
                      {
                      "question":  "Which of the following words are included in the definition/derivation of the word ‘Frugal?’",
                      "choices": [ "Virtuous", "To Enjoy","Cheap","Of The Essence","A, B, & D"],
                      "correctChoice": "A, B, & D",
                      "score": 5
                      
                      },
                      {
                      "question":  "In what year is it estimated that the cumulative GDP of emerging markets (excluding China) will surpass that of the developed world?",
                      "choices": [ 2014, 2016,2022,2031],
                      "correctChoice": 2016,
                      "score": 5
                      
                      },
                      {
                      "question":  "Which of the following is the first step of the Design Innovation Process?",
                      "choices": [ "Define", "Prototype","Ideate","Empathize","Test"],
                      "correctChoice": "Empathize",
                      "score": 5
                      },
                      {
                      "question":  "What percentage of the world now has access to a mobile phone?",
                      "choices": [ 28, 46, 59, 81, 97],
                      "correctChoice": 81,
                      "score": 5
                      },
                      {
                      "question":  "What is ‘reverse innovation’?",
                      "choices": [ "Learning how to design a product by breaking it apart and seeing how it was built.", "Engineering for the emerging market consumer before the developed world consumer.","An innovation that is developed in an emerging market and is eventually utilized in a mature market."],
                      "correctChoice": "An innovation that is developed in an emerging market and is eventually utilized in a mature market.",
                      "score": 5
                      }
                      
    ];

    var geography = [
                      {
                      "question":  "What is the capital of Iceland?",
                      "choices": [ "Helsinki", "Dublin","Oslo","Reykjayik"],
                      "correctChoice": "Reykjayik",
                      "score": 5
                      
                      },
                      {
                      "question":  "The Baikonur Cosmodrome, the world's largest space launching facility, is located in which former Soviet country?",
                      "choices": ["Estonia","Georgia","Kazakhstan","Ukraine"],
                      "correctChoice":"Kazakhstan" ,
                      "score": 5
                      
                      },
                      {
                      "question":  "The Yellow Sea lies between China and which other country?",
                      "choices": ["South Korea","Philippines","Indonesia","Taiwan"],
                      "correctChoice": "South Korea",
                      "score": 5
                      },
                      {
                      "question":  "Which country occupies most of Anatolia, also known as Asia Minor?",
                      "choices": [ "Saudi Arabia", "India", "Hungary", "Turkey"],
                      "correctChoice": "Turkey",
                      "score": 5
                      },
                      {
                      "question":  "Which country lies on the equator?",
                      "choices": [ "Brazil", "Mexico", "Chile", "Argentina"],
                      "correctChoice": "Brazil",
                      "score": 5
                      }
                      
    ];
